So opposite of hands to stand on, let's see what hands are to improve on.
You know what I was trying to say, right?
Well, there's one because we only have one pair.
So you're going to try to improve instead of staying, and we'll make it three of a kind.
Again, well you can certainly stand of three Kings, of course.
There's two pair, you can stand on that.
Look at that!
I rolled Queens, three Queens.
So, I'm getting lucky here.
Okay!
There's a pair of Aces.
You know, half the time I'm going to try to improve on that, I'm going to give it one more roll see what happens.
Well, no deal, I'm going to give it another roll.
I've got two pair, so now my opponent has to make two pair in three rolls.
Specifically he has to make two pair where one of the pair are Aces and then the other pair is higher than tens.
So, but these that's improving on a roll, that's a demonstration of that.